

Charles Maina

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology a

Experience: 2 years Available: 1 Week Location: Nairobi

About Me

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language),Django,Flask, Microsoft Excel, HTML, Software Development, and Microsoft Office. Strong engineering professional with a software development focused in full-stack from moringa school.

Work Experience

Bluewave International

Graduate trainee | Programmer Nairobi , Kenya 2016-08-01 | 2016-12-01

Programmer.

Lead a team of four in projects given.

o Competa millman

Graduate trainee | Software developer Nairobi , Kenya 2019-08-01 | 2019-12-01

Tested functionalities of a software. Developed softwares and websites.

Education

Software Development

Certificate | software development

Bachelor in Business Information Technology

Bachelor | BBIT

Job Skills

Python, Django, Flask, HTML

Angular, CSS

PHP

React.Js

Language Skills

- English
- ∘ Swahili



Projects & Portfolios

○ My Portfolio

https://charlesmurage.github.io/portfolio/

